var jsonData=
[
                {
                "question" : "Which  team won the 2019 World Cup ?",
                "opt1" : " Sri Lanka ",
                "opt2" : " England ",
                "opt3" : " New Zealand ",
                "opt4" : " India ",
                "answer" : " England "
                },
                {
                "question" : " In 2019 World Cup india was knocked out by?",
                "opt1" : " South Africa  ",
                "opt2" : " England ",
                "opt3" : " Afghanistan ",
                "opt4" : " New Zealand ",
                "answer" : " New Zealand "
                },
                {
                "question" : "Which batsman registered the highest individual score at the 2019 World Cup?",
                "opt1" : " Roy ",
                "opt2" : " Finch ",
                "opt3" : " Warner ",
                "opt4" : " Kolhi ",
                "answer" : " Warner "
                },
                {
                "question" : "Which batsman hit 17 sixes during his 71-ball 148 against Afghanistan at Old Trafford, surpassing the record for maximums in a single ODI innings?",
                "opt1" : " Finch ",
                "opt2" : " Stokes ",
                "opt3" : " Morgan ",
                "opt4" : " Maxwell ",
                "answer" : " Morgan "
                },
                {
                "question" : "Which bowler recorded the best bowling figures in the tournament?",
                "opt1" : " Starc ",
                "opt2" : " Afridi ",
                "opt3" : " Archer ",
                "opt4" : " Shami ",
                "answer" : " Afridi "
                },
                {
                "question" : "Which bowler took hat-trick at lord's ?",
                "opt1" : " Starc  ",
                "opt2" : " Boult ",
                "opt3" : " Archer ",
                "opt4" : " Shami ",
                "answer" : " Boult "
                },
                {
                "question" : "Against which side did Afghanistan register a score of 288 all out in 50 overs - their highest in a men's World Cup game?",
                "opt1" : " West Indies ",
                "opt2" : " England ",
                "opt3" : " India ",
                "opt4" : " New Zealand ",
                "answer" : " West Indies "
                },
                {
                "question" : "Which batting pair's 192 was the highest partnership of this World Cup?",
                "opt1" : " Warner & Usman khawaja ",
                "opt2" : " Rohit & Rahul ",
                "opt3" : " Roy & Bairstow ",
                "opt4" : " Root & Morgan ",
                "answer" : " Warner & Usman khawaja "
                },
                {
                "question" : "Who achieved the record for the highest score by a No. 8 batsman at a men's World Cup?",
                "opt1" : " coulter-nile ",
                "opt2" : " Jadeja ",
                "opt3" : " brathwaite ",
                "opt4" : " boult ",
                "answer" : " coulter-nile "
                },
                {
                "question" : "Who was the oldest cricketer played in WC 2019?",
                "opt1" : " Dhoni ",
                "opt2" : " Gayle ",
                "opt3" : " Malik ",
                "opt4" : " Tahir ",
                "answer" : " Tahir "
                }    
 ]